<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News &#8211; Our Corporate Responsibility</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 11:10:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2024/02/cropped-cropped-zxxczx-32x32.png</url>
	<title>News &#8211; Our Corporate Responsibility</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>US sanctions alleged funding network used by Iran’s IRGC and Hezbollah</title>
		<link>/us-sanctions-alleged-funding-network-used-by-irans-irgc-and-hezbollah/</link>
					<comments>/us-sanctions-alleged-funding-network-used-by-irans-irgc-and-hezbollah/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 11:10:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=10987</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The US announced new sanctions on Wednesday against two companies based in Lebanon and another in Turkey for their links to Iran-backed Hezbollah and the Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps-Quds Force. “The IRGC-QF and its proxy network persist in their attempts to generate revenue from illicit commercial activity that funds terrorism and destabilizing activities in the ... <a title="US sanctions alleged funding network used by Iran’s IRGC and Hezbollah" class="read-more" href="/us-sanctions-alleged-funding-network-used-by-irans-irgc-and-hezbollah/" aria-label="More on US sanctions alleged funding network used by Iran’s IRGC and Hezbollah">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The US announced new sanctions on Wednesday against two companies based in Lebanon and another in Turkey for their links to Iran-backed Hezbollah and the Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps-Quds Force.</p>
<p>“The IRGC-QF and its proxy network persist in their attempts to generate revenue from illicit commercial activity that funds terrorism and destabilizing activities in the region,” State Department Spokesman Matt Miller said.</p>
<p>The Treasury Department said the sanctioned companies had generated hundreds of millions of dollars’ worth of revenue from selling Iranian commodities, including to the Syrian government.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/us-sanctions-alleged-funding-network-used-by-irans-irgc-and-hezbollah/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Egypt reach initial deal, pound to undergo swift devaluation</title>
		<link>/egypt-reach-initial-deal-pound-to-undergo-swift-devaluation/</link>
					<comments>/egypt-reach-initial-deal-pound-to-undergo-swift-devaluation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 11:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=10985</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Egypt has reached a preliminary agreement with the International Monetary Fund (IMF) on a revised loan, a government official told Al-Arabiya and Al-Hadath channels on Wednesday. The agreement includes an immediate devaluation of the Egyptian pound and an increase in the financing program from $3 billion to $7 billion or more, along with an extension ... <a title="Egypt reach initial deal, pound to undergo swift devaluation" class="read-more" href="/egypt-reach-initial-deal-pound-to-undergo-swift-devaluation/" aria-label="More on Egypt reach initial deal, pound to undergo swift devaluation">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Egypt has reached a preliminary agreement with the International Monetary Fund (IMF) on a revised loan, a government official told Al-Arabiya and Al-Hadath channels on Wednesday.</p>
<p>The agreement includes an immediate devaluation of the Egyptian pound and an increase in the financing program from $3 billion to $7 billion or more, along with an extension of its duration.</p>
<p>The official highlighted that the key feature of the agreement is the swift devaluation of the Egyptian pound to narrow the disparity between the official and parallel market rates of the pound against the dollar.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/egypt-reach-initial-deal-pound-to-undergo-swift-devaluation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>IRGC chief says Iran does not fear war with US</title>
		<link>/irgc-chief-says-iran-does-not-fear-war-with-us/</link>
					<comments>/irgc-chief-says-iran-does-not-fear-war-with-us/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 11:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=10983</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[US threats against Iran will not be left unanswered, the chief commander of the Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps said on Wednesday, adding that Tehran is not afraid of direct military confrontation with Washington. “These days, we hear some threats from American officials, to whom we say … we do not leave any threat unanswered and ... <a title="IRGC chief says Iran does not fear war with US" class="read-more" href="/irgc-chief-says-iran-does-not-fear-war-with-us/" aria-label="More on IRGC chief says Iran does not fear war with US">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>US threats against Iran will not be left unanswered, the chief commander of the Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps said on Wednesday, adding that Tehran is not afraid of direct military confrontation with Washington.</p>
<p>“These days, we hear some threats from American officials, to whom we say … we do not leave any threat unanswered and we do not seek war but we are not afraid of war,” state media quoted IRGC head Hossein Salami as saying.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/irgc-chief-says-iran-does-not-fear-war-with-us/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/

Object Caching 32/43 objects using Redis
Page Caching using Redis 
Database Caching using Redis

Served from: _ @ 2024-02-01 11:10:56 by W3 Total Cache
-->